Bear to be different
Norm of the North is a adventure, animation,
comedy film directed by Trevor Wall.
Polar bear Norm and his three Arctic lemming buddies are forced out into the
world once their icy home begins melting and breaking apart.
Landing in New York, Norm begins life anew as a performing corporate mascot, only to discover that
his new employers are directly responsible for the destruction of his polar home.
Norm (voice), played by Rob Schneider.
Vera (voice), played by Heather Graham.
Olympia (voice), played by Maya Kay.
Mr. Greene (voice), played by Ken Jeong.
Socrates (voice), played by Bill Nighy.
Grandfather (voice), played by Colm Meaney.
Norm of the North is a 2016 animated adventure
comedy film directed by Trevor Wall.
The film features the voices of Rob Schneider, Heather Graham, Ken Jeong, Colm Meaney, Loretta Devine, Gabriel Iglesias,
Michael McElhatton, and Bill Nighy, and is an international co-production of the United States, India, and Ireland.
Norm of the North was theatrically released on January 15, 2016 by Lionsgate.
The film received negative reviews from critics, and
grossed $30 million against a budget of $7–18M.
It spawned three direct-to-video sequels: Norm of the North: Keys to the Kingdom, Norm of
the North: King Sized Adventure, and Norm of the North: Family Vacation.
The film explores themes of new york city, polar bear, arctic
polar circle region, computer animation, psychotic.
The tone is lighthearted.